(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T12:24:04.331379",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I'm Gigi Murin.
I used to be 14 years old in eighth grade, but now I'm not.
I'm a bit clumsy, crazy and silly,
and I may not look it, but actually, I'm a member of Hololive English Justice.
That's true.
Every day is just the same old thing,
people always look at my face and they're like, "What is that?"
And my big, big hieroglyph is a mystery. I don't really know why.
Lately called the "fister", 'cause I fister people, you know? You know what I mean?
Today is the day of a very important Justice meeting, but I absolutely overslept.
So I have to hurry up and make sure to look both ways before crossing the road.
And... go!
Ouch!
Who is that?
That is so weird.
Where am I?
A beautiful 2D fantasy world?
Also, I'm so efficient that I can shoot vinyl records out of my car.
Even though I've only been driving for five minutes.
Hit them with a car, and it'll be really cool. What the—?
A horse? That's not a truck.
That's dangerous! I could have died.
But phew! That gremlin sure knows how to drive. Gremlin—!
Ugh... My body hurts...
I feel like I got run over by something, but I don't know what.
Oh, is that a statue of a gremlin? Looks cool.
Wait a second.
I know this.
I've been isekaied!
What the freak? Gigi, you're here too?
This? Justice cardboard?
Gigi, what's going on?
Where are we?
What are you guys doing? Why are you cardboard?
Why does Cecelia look so sad?
How dare you do this to us!
This is your fault somehow!
I don't know how you did this, you little—
Oh, you look terrible!
Well, let's go investigate around here.
Let's go. Okay.
I'm on my way! Wait, guys, wait for me! We can have an adventure together—
Horses! Two of them!
Goodbye, leaving heartache of the past behind,
there's no more—
Looking back, it's time
moving down our own path
ever more voyaging forward to make this journey last
Never spoken about in the light
like a promise found riding the wind
where an abyss begins spiraling outward and up
an inspiring tale begins
We who dared to fight changing of times
us who follow unreachable dreams
Know it's here and right now that we're drawn to somehow
deep inside, we'll till the world will leap
Little twists aching
wandering near and far
touching lives just like ours
blinding fires
till I've wasted away
One day
I'll recall
these nights are relentless
pressing onward
We never surrender
Toward the skies, we can rise
again
I was hit by a truck and reincarnated as the protagonist in a fantasy world but then a horse ran me over and now all my friends are cardboard?
[Title: I was hit by a truck and reincarnated as the protagonist in a fantasy world but then a horse ran me over and now all my friends are cardboard?]
If anything else hits me, I don't think I'll survive much longer.
I really need to be more careful.
Thank goodness I'm still alive.
The winds whispered of your coming... and now, here you are.
Who are you?!
I am the greatest wizard in all of Grem Kingdom.
Wizard Oji-chan.
Wizard Oji-chan? Are you a wizard or Oji-chan? What should I call you?
So many of Grem's warriors have fallen, one by one...
...while we waited for your arrival!
Okay...
The wait was worth it! You are far more powerful than I ever imagined a hero could be!
He's not responding to me. He's probably an NPC. Is this a game?
NPC?! Hah! NPC?!
I'm sorry! I didn't know you could talk!
I'm sorry...
You're the key.
Without you, your friend and this world are lost...
What? Lost? What are you talking about?
Gigi... the world is waiting...
That's my name. That's me. I'm the hero! I'm going to save the world from being cardboard!
Hah!
Ah! What did you do to me?! It hurts! It hurts!
Hah! Get that out of here! What is this?!
Hah! Woah! Now I'm so cute and soft and fluffy now! Friend with you? Purchase next time they're in stock?
Hold on! Wait! Let me redo it! I'll do it properly this time! I don't understand.
Okey okey okey! Moikarasete! Hah!
Squeak! Squeak squeak! Two friends! Squeak! Calls down the abyss! Squeak squeak!
Look! Gigi! I'm ready! Gigi! Go! Budit! Hah!
Agh! Ah! Wait! I think I'm in motion now! What is...
What is this?
Hands? You did it! You've done it!
Oh my god!
Look how, how cute I am!
Aw, I've always been cute.
But now, now it's even cuter. Now everyone can see how cute I...
Look at that fat tail! Look at that fat...
I can do everything!
I can't do that.
Watch this, guys! You never seen this before?
Okay, okay. Whee!
Whee! I can do everything!
Two in a row? Just kidding.
I have a world to save! Look at that!
Everyone loves me! Gigi Mourning!
Chikara da! Shyo!
Oh, I'm so dizzy.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
What? What should I do to save everyone?
Ugh, the world is spinning.
Ow.
Before saving everyone of them,
let's see if you can survive basic chores.
Basic? I can do basic chores.
Let's start with...
A bird?
Start with what?
What? What are we starting with?
A wing?
A wing? Go with what?
What? What?
What did you do? What did you do with the muffins?!
No, no, no! Go down, go down, go down on there!
Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
No! No!
Ahahahaha!
The birds took him!
I knew I could never trust a bird!
Hey you, Come here! Follow me!
A Grem?
Um, I have to help my, my friend.
You're scared and lost... Not knowing what to do, right?
I'll show you how to save your friends. Follow me!
Oh, okay.
Is there some moss?
This is weird.
This place is dark and it smells bad.
Hey, it smells good! Do exactly as I say if you want to save your friends!
Go to the Grem kingdom and return with the One Ping, a Straw Hat, and a Honkshoe.
Why do you need them?
YOU DON'T GET TO ASK ME ANY QUESTIONS! NOW GO GIGI, GOOOOOO!!
Okay.
Whoa!
So this is the Grem kingdom?
It's so cool! There's so many Grems!
Does this mean this entire kingdom is mine if I save it?
Whoa, there's so many of you.
Not, not all at once! No, no, no, no, no!
What?
Oh, I can't hear you.
Let's, let's try this Grem. Lucky little Grem, what's on your mind?
Things aren't going well with my partner... I need your help to fix our relationship.
Aw, that is not my problem.
Ah, okay. How about this Grem? Do you have anything interesting to say to me?
My tummy is getting very large and I don't know why. Please come with me to the doctor.
Okay, a little Glossy Grem, pregnant.
Okay, how about this one?
Make a contract with me, and become a magical girl!
Oh, that is not my problem either. Oh, no, no, no, no, no! I will not be doing that.
I know what happens when you sign a contract! You should never put your name down on things.
Well, these Grems were useless.
I think if I use my RPG knowledge, you're supposed to get information from NPCs out of store!
And there's so many stalls near me!
Ah, let's go to this one.
So cute! Aw.
Are you a little worker Grem?
Aw, yeah, how much do you make an hour? Do you make enough to survive?
Aw, what is this?
For me?
Hay?
Uh, that's decorative hay, not edible...
(chewing noises)
Can I ask you something? Who's the strongest person around here?
Where can I get the One Ping?
Then, here is the Quest for you! Take this ring and throw it into a volcano to destroy it.
This cursed ring holds centuries of anger. To purify it, it must be thrown into a volcano... but we fear fire and can't go near it.
Oh, okay. Yeah, I can do that quest for you. Don't worry, I'm the chosen one!
A ring! Wow!
How is this supposed to help me? Save Justice! They're gonna die! They're gonna die in the volcano eruptions! Oh wait, I don't know what a volcano is.
Let's just try to find the One Ping myself.
Wait, this box looks a little suspicious.
Deliver to weapon shop.
Oh, cool. Is this for a quest?
Okay.
Hey, I got a package! I got you guys a package. It's a gift from me!
I bought this. I'll just leave it right here.
Your BL novels?
No, no, no. Don't lose sight of the quest, Gigi.
Whoa! This is a really cool sword! If only I could save Justice with—
Oh my god.
This sword's really cool. How much is it?
What's that? $5?
I can't afford that. But how about I save them to the power of friendship?!
Is the One Ping even real?
Okay, sounds easy. I can do that.
What? I don't think that's how you craft an iron bar.
Where did I get over here? Where are my sunglasses? This bitch is kind of nasty! Who let you have this in a shoe store?
Oh, okay. I guess we're really doing this.
Set on a quest to save my friends,
I don't really know what rhymes with friends,
Old man wizard, take it from me,
Evil flying birds looking for a treat,
Don't even know if he's alive or not,
But who really cares what the premises that I got?
Horest girls raisin', my heart is pacin',
Got me on my knees, making skill activations,
Then a bunch of grems surrounded me,
To ask me to force some iron bars, you see,
Wait, a second,
Starting to realize what you meant by bars,
Put my rap game in fire,
And my dancing not desired,
But if there's one thing that I'm not, it's definitely not a liar,
So I hope you don't mind if I twerk up on you, ya see,
There's a promise that I made to Fauna,
Yeah, oh, I twerked it!
Ah, I don't know how to twerk.
I don't want to put in the work,
You see, twerking is a skill you have to get the train up for, everyone,
And I ran out of rhymes 30 seconds ago.
All right, um...
I got dance moves, and then...
Okay, I can't do that.
Mic drop.
Really? You liked it?
Yippee! I got that iron bars!
Yippee!
Is that... is that what I think it is?
The One Ping is real!
Oh, where's my gauntlets?
Could I have it?
Could I have them?
Oh, cool. Thanks. I'm gonna go now.
Mmm, meat come me... I'm so hungry.
I can't save Justice like this.
Meat? For me? For free?
Whoa, big ass hat.
Whoa, big-ass hat.
No, no. I think your hat is lovely. I love it.
Nom nom, thank you.
I'm looking for a straw hat. Any way you can buy one?
Oh, here we go again.
Giant rats? Where do I find one of those?
Whoa. Is this a family of 26 rats?
I guess I can see why you want pictures of them. Oh, okay.
It's picture time.
I'll get pictures of all 26 of them. Oh yeah!
Get in the frame. Let me get a picture of you.
One of them doesn't even look like a rat. That's a really big person.
Right, one more. One more. That's a crab!
What are you doing? You're not even a rat!
Okay. What about down here?
And look at those! They look just like Justice.
If Justice were rats, but they're cardboard.
Whoa. Okay.
Don't worry. I got you. I got every angle imaginable.
That's a computer mouse.
And look at this one I took, and then this one,
and then this one, and it was so cute!
All these rats are so cute and this is awesome.
And this is a yummy looking rat. Yay!
A hat? For me? Yay!
Now I have two items!
Oh, the stables are over there.
Maybe I can get the honkshoe from a stable.
You scared me.
Bad! I'm doing bad!
It's like no one cares about me.
This cruel evil world... The stables!
Aw, our horses. Aw, hello.
Hi! Hi there. Hey!
I can share.
Here you go. Eat up.
Is this horse okay?
Oh, no. I think he's sleeping. Okay, I think I can just...
Don't mind if I...
I'll just take this. You don't need this, do you?
I've done it! I've gathered all three items by myself! Yay!
I am the hero of this kingdom!
Sewer Grem, you probably didn't think
I'd get them all, but I did.
I got everything because I am the hero!
Dosou for you.
Are you really? Are you really?
Oh, man.
Can't believe I got everything.
Does that mean I saved Justice?
Oh, they're going to be so proud of me.
Wait, is there something?
No, no, please! No! Don't do it! No! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Oh, wait!
Why does this keep happening to me?
Where am I?
What is this?
Is this my fantasy life?
A house?
Where am I going? What is...
Ah.
Hey everyone! What's... How's it going, guys?
Oh wait, I missed the first one.
Hello, everyone!
My name is Bae,
and my name is Biboo.
And together we are...
BiBoo!
Welcome, welcome to our Let's Play.
Guys, we're playing a new game called... What is it called? What is it called?
Gigi's Gym? Gigi's Gym?
It's a brand new game, guys.
With the rat and me, Alpha.
We are the first ones to touch it.
So we got exclusive footage here for you today.
Thank you so much! Let's get started.
The premise of this game is your character is...
Gigi? What are you doing over there?
Is it Gigi? Gigi? Gigi? Gigi? Probably Gigi. I don't know.
And it's kind of like a real life simulator game.
So if I push this button right here,
she should be able to sit down.
Oh, let's see. Oh, there we go!
What? I didn't do that!
Oh, the control is... Let's test them out more.
Let's test out the controls. Let's try more complicated ones.
Can it make me sit on the sofa?
Let's see if she can act like a dog.
You got that dog in you. You got the dog in you.
Of course, of course!
Make me act like a dog.
Louder!
Louder! Woof, woof, woof! Look at the physics!
Okay, that's not... That's pretty good. Okay, shut up, shut up, shut up.
So this is just the base game, right?
So you know, there's the rooms.
At the moment, we've got the main living room, we've got the bedroom and the bathroom.
I think there's a kitchen attached, a kitchenette.
Should we go check out the kitchen?
Yeah, let's go see the kitchen.
Move to the kitchen. Move to the kitchen.
Come on. I don't want to.
Anything we can interact with within the kitchen?
Control is broken? Oh no.
Oh, look! A knife! Pick up... Pick up the knife! Pick it up right now!
What does she have? A knife!
Pick up a knife! Pick up a knife! No!
Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up!
Why is there's so much input lag?
I know. Why is there input lag?
Maybe the connection is just a little bit slow. That's fine.
Okay, now what?
Into the store!
Yes, into the...
You think they accounted for this?
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! Maybe that's something that can add to the next update.
That was kind of anticlimactic, oh well.
I can pick up knife again?
Pick up knife? Always carry a knife.
Should we move into another room?
Let's go into door number one. Let's see what's in there.
Walk forwards. Go.
What is in that door?
Oh, she clipped into the wall. Oh, she clipped into the wall.
So we gotta report that bug.
Oh, there's a bathtub and there's a toilet.
Oh, I know, I know! Have you heard of Skibidi Toilet?
Oh, gosh! What is Skibidi Toilet?
I'm going to make the character phase into the toilet.
Become one with the toilet, now!
Skibidi toilet! I learn something new every day.
Yes, yes, yes, put it up, put it up! Yes!
Unhappy!
This is Skibidi toilet, is she happy?
Of course, she could be.
Spin your head around. Spin your head around.
This is great!
If you guys like what you see, make sure you like and subscribe!
Okay, sure! Skibidi toilet.
Wow, okay.
I hope you enabled notifications so you don't miss the next episode!
So you don't miss the next episode!
Yeah,
there's going to be more,
and people, thank you for watching!
Bye!
I'm gone?
I don't hear their voices anymore.
Oh, thank God!
Oh, get me out of this toilet! Every damn time! Give me the toilet!
First, you take over my body, and you give me the damn toilet!
How do I get out of here?
How could How could they torture me like this?
How could— how could they torture me like this?
Why do they make me do all those things?
And they didn't even feed me!
And they didn't even say that I was a good girl after they made me do all those things!
And they didn't even say I was a good girl after making me do all those things!
And now I'm poor...
I'm just gonna take it out on this canvas.
If I just paint what I want, then maybe I'll be rewarded for it.
Because I am... Karma comes to good people. So... beautiful woman.
Boobs.
Yes. Yes! I've done it!
My greatest work yet! My painting!
Gigi?
Hello? Knock knock.
Are you in there? Okay, I'm going to come in.
Oh my goodness...
This absolute masterpiece.
One of the lost works of Picasso, or no? It has to be Leonardo da Vinci.
It's so incredible, I've never seen anything like it.
I can't believe that something like this is before my own eyes.
I can't believe something like this is before my own eyes.
Gigi!
Gigi, wake up!
Gigi, are you all right?
Something attacked you? Oh, I don't know what kind of...
Why are you snoring? Oh, beautiful woman...
Yes, it's me. I came over just like you invited me to. Marissa Ravencroft?
Yes, it's me. I came over just like you invited me to. Nerissa Ravencroft?
Yes, it is I.
Is that you? And that's a painting?
No, but did you make this, Gigi? I made this. It's incredible. Do you like it?
I do. In fact, I thought of you while making it. Can you tell?
I can. In fact, if if it's so, that I'm your muse,
I can. In fact, if it's so that I'm your muse,
maybe we could be together?
Really? Yes, no one's ever said that to me before.
I've I've never wanted anything quite as much after seeing this painting.
I've never wanted anything quite as much after seeing this painting.
The fire of my heart has been inflamed, and I feel like I cannot live without you, Gigi Murin. So...
Don't scream now.
You're tickling me.
You know what? I've thought a lot of thinking. Thought about thinking, I've thought of it, and I've come up with a thing: we should get married.
You know what? I've thought a lot. Thought about thinking, I've thought of it, and I've come up with a thing: we should get married.
Oh, I thought you'd never ask. Really? Really? Why would you think that?
Do you want me? I want you so bad.
You have no idea how bad I want you.
Let's go. We've never touched on how to consummate our marriage.
What? What? I don't know if I'm ready for that!
I don't know! I don't know!
そう単純な祈りだった
That's right - it had begun as a simple prayer.
端から段々と消える寒暖
Gradually fading away from the start.
今から朱殷が上がるから
The curtain is about to rise now,
静かな会場を後にさようなら
So saying goodbye as we leave the quiet venue behind.
愛のネタバレ
Spoilers of love,
「別れ」っぽいな
it seems like "farewell."
人生のネタバレ
Spoilers of life,
「死ぬ」っぽいな
it seems like "death."
なにそれ意味深で
What's with that, so profound...
かっこいいじゃん...
and cool...
それっぽい単語集で
With a collection of buzzwords like that,
踊ってんだ
you're dancing away.
失敬
Disrespectful.
気が滅入った 嫌なことが
Feeling depressed, unable to even
自分さえ抱えきれずもてあました それを守っている
hold onto my own unpleasant things, I'm protecting it.
淀んだ声はからからに
A muddy voice, dried out,
喉は焼けてうまくすれ
my throat is burning, I can't even swallow well—
てくすれないを言うべきか から抜いて
what should I say? Pulling it out of the empty air.
感じてたものが遠く離れ去っていた
What I felt was drifting far away.
同じような違うんだか違う
Is it the same or different? Somehow different.
いつまでいこうか どこまで行けるのか
How much longer can I go? How far can I go?
さらけ出さないなら何想うの？
If you won't reveal it, what are you thinking?
僕らが跳ねるなら 僕らが舞うなら
If we're going to leap, if we're going to dance,
その度に何回も繋がれるように
so that every time we connect,
ここにいとけるなら
if we can stay here,
離さずいられたら
if we could stay without letting go,
まだ誰も知らない 隔てなく笑うという
laughing without a gap that nobody knows yet—
エイッ ステテテッテイエッ
Eiya, stetetette ieh!
神っぽいな それもうもっと代わりにナス
It's god-ish, make that more of a replacement.
一生はとももわりはなか
A lifetime is temporary, not long.
急楽とは 嘘でなる
Pleasure built on lies will become...
ほこぼうまえに ここをととわこがど
Before it crumbles, where is the beating heart?
都合のいい願いを 同じように同じようにささやく
Murmuring convenient wishes over and over.
どこから聞こえる？ 何を見失うか？
Where can I hear it? What am I losing sight of?
さらけ出さないから ことばはこげない
Because I won't reveal it, words won't burn.
僕らが跳ねるなら 僕らが舞うなら
If we're going to leap, if we're going to dance,
その度に何回も 逃げ出せるように
so that every time we can escape,
ここにいとけるなら 壊われないように
if we can stay here, so it won't break,
互いに隠して からだをあずけてよ
hide it from each other and entrust our bodies to it.
なるなるの ラルルラルダ ラルルラルダ
Narunaru no laruru raruda laruru raruda
君となら 君となら 君とこ？ 君とと？ 君とだ！
With you, with you, with you? With you? With you!
いつまで続くのだろうと
Wondering how long this will continue,
同じように同じようにつぶやく
murmuring the same thing over and over.
今は忘れないよう 刻まれた空気を
So I won't forget now, the engraved air—
これから何度 思い出すのだろうだるだ
how many times will I remember it from now on?
僕らが跳ねるなら 僕らが舞うなら
If we're going to leap, if we're going to dance,
その度に何回も 繋がれるように
so that every time we connect,
ここにいとけるなら 話さずいられたら
if we can stay here, if we could stay without letting go,
まだ誰も知らない 感覚で僕の
with a feeling nobody knows yet,
生きてるすべてを 確かめて正しくして
verifying and righting everything about my living self.
エイッ ステテテッテイエッ
Eiya, stetetette ieh!
Oh, husband... I'm so happy to be living a domestic life with you, Gigi-moodin.
Well, in your awesome house, with your awesome kitchen, and your awesome floor, and this awesome couch,
wife.
Husband?
I've never been married before.
Me neither.
What am I supposed to do? How am I supposed to take care of you?
Take care of me? You're so sweet, no one's ever wanted to do that. I want to take care of you.
Just I've dreamed of this forever and ever.
"Since I've dreamed of this forever and ever."
Gigi-moodin!
Please, not in front of—not in front of the studio audience!
Woah, oh, my beautiful, beautiful wife, how far does your leg go up?
As far as you want it to.
I see. That's enough. Not in front of the studio audience.
Not in front of the studio audience.
I can't believe you did that.
Me? If you say so, husband, I can't believe I'm such a dirty, dirty girl,
in front of this audience and everything. That's only for me, my dirty, dirty girl!
Yes! I wouldn't want anyone else to see me like that, but you. I should do something for you.
That is what a Gigi-moodin should do.
Yes, I would love that. I should make you some toast.
Some toast for me? Yes, for you. You're so sweet.
Have you ever cooked before?
No, never.
Never.
I I don't even know how to use a microwave.
I don't even know how to use a microwave.
Really?
Yes, really.
Well, I only have one thing here and it's toast.
Wow, you're so amazing.
Did you make the bread yourself too?
I made it.
Woah!
Whoa!
Oh, it's been on the floor, that's even better!
You stepped there!
Watch me, watch me flip it, okay?
Yes, yes, I'm watching.
Oh. Oh.
Watch, watch this.
Wait, wait!
Here, wait, I have a solution.
Okay, flip it.
Yes! You're amazing!
That made me really hungry.
Do you mind if I eat this toast first?
Of course you can.
Anything for you, so why?
That looks tasty.
Have these bathroom my sweet. Oh, of course.
By all means, anything you need.
If I look through the door knob hole, I can see Gigi on the toilet.
Oh Gigi, I just have to tell you, these last few hours together have been absolute domestic bliss.
I don't think there's any moment in my life that has been as amazing as this.
Are you still in there?
Oh, sorry.
How's the toast?
It's really good.
I wish you could try some.
Oh, yeah, me too.
Maybe next time.
So I had to whatever was poisoned, you know?
So I had to check.
You're so thoughtful.
Nerissa Ravencroft, I've been doing a lot of thinking while I was on the toilet.
Nerissa Ravenfield, I've been doing a lot of thinking while I was on the toilet.
Yes.
Don't say another word.
I don't know what a family entails.
I completely understand.
Will you be able to teach me?
Of course, I can teach you anything.
Really?
Of course.
We can do anything you want together.
You can teach me anything?
Anything.
Anything your heart desires.
I shouldn't keep my beautiful wife waiting.
Yes. But I have a tummy ache.
You have a tummy ache?
Will you wait for me?
Of course, I'll wait forever for you.
Okay, hold on.
I don't think I should be eating this toast all by myself.
Don't worry.
Let me slide it under the door for you.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
Is it good? So delicious.
Is it tasty?
It's so tasty.
Never has there been bread made this amazing.
I'm glad that I made such a beautiful toast for you.
Me too. It was my first time.
Hey!
I finished it all.
All of it?
All of it. It's all in my stomach.
Is it really yummy?
So delicious.
I'm glad.
I still am nervous.
Because you're so you're so beautiful and I'm just a little guy on a toilet.
There's so much wrong with me.
There's everything right with you.
Well, that's how I feel about you.
Really?
With me, everything is wrong, but when we're together, everything is perfect.
My love, why are you crying?
No one's ever said that to me before.
I'm sick and tired of these walls separating us.
Nerissa, come in here.
Let's break them down.
Sit on my lap, Nerissa.
Sit on your lap?
I will.
Anything you ask for, I will do.
How about though we move from this porcelain?
My porcelain throne?
Yeah, and we move somewhere a little more comfortable.
I'm I'm done.
Yeah?
Wash my hand?
Okay, it's better this way.
Let's hold hands.
Yes, let's hold hands. Let's go to the bedroom together.
Yeah, to the bedroom.
Well, Gigi,
What's the matter?
I'm shy.
Don't be shy.
I've never done this before.
You know, Gigi, the truth is, I know I said I'd teach you anything, but
I've never done this before either.
Really?
Then how are we supposed to do it if you've never
You're done such a thing?
You've done such a thing?
Who's going to teach me?
We're going to learn together.
You can just learn from nothing?
Of course.
That's, you know, some You can just do that.
That's, you know... You can just do that.
We'll find it out.
How do you think the first humans
learned things, Gigi?
I don't know.
Why are you asking me that?
Philosophical. It's pillow talk. Anyway.
Oh, oh. Okay.
Well... shall we?
Well... now that you've brought it up,
um, the first humans probably
learned things by doing...
Yes!
So let's just do it then.
Okay!
I can't wait another moment.
That was enough!
That's too much!
That was way too much!
Gigi Murin, you monster!
I'm sorry!
I was trying to be really gentle.
It was great.
Really?
Yes, it was amazing.
Well, I'm glad that we could spend
our first day in the bedroom together as a married couple.
our first day as a married couple.
Yes, but Gigi, there's something strange going on.
Yes, but Gigi, there's something
strange going on.
Did you transfer your stomach ache to me?
I don't think so. You can't just give a stomach ache to someone.
I don't think so. You can't just
give a stomach ache to someone.
But it really hurts. Maybe you need to use the bathroom?
But it really hurts. Maybe
you need to use the bathroom?
I don't think so, but oh.
Gigi.
What?
Wait a moment.
Gigi, your fingers!
No!
No, I'm not ready! I'm not ready!
You forgot to wear full clothes!
No!
How is it?
I can't. We can't. We don't have the money!
Gigi, I'm sorry.
You didn't tell you to get this.
The house is barely holding together!
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor, please! My wife, she's in pain. Can you please help her? Please, doctor!
Doctor, please! My wife, she's in pain.
Can you please help her? Please, doctor!
Please help me!
Hello? Are you going to help her? Hello?
Why are you laughing?
She's giving birth here! She's literally...
She is literally giving birth, and you're just laughing at her?
What kind of doctor? I will go on the internet and leave bad reviews about you. Your days are numbered. You're going to go out of business and you're going to go bankrupt!
What kind of doctor? I will go on the internet
and leave bad reviews about you.
Your days are numbered, you're going
to go out of business and bankrupt!
Baby, we won't wait another minute!
Wait!
Gigi, I got it. Can you save? It's our child. It's our baby. It's a... It's a beautiful egg.
Gigi, I got it. Can you save?
It's our child. It's our baby.
It's a... It's a beautiful egg.
It is such a beautiful egg.
We didn't need a doctor after all.
You're natural.
We're so good at that.
It seems like we're both a natural at a lot of things.
Yes. You know, I'm a little impatient. I kind of wonder, what are you? What are you in there? Hello?
Yes. You know, I'm a little impatient.
I kind of wonder, what are you?
What are you in there? Hello?
Hey. Are you... Hello?
Are you going to just shake the baby?
Yeah. Wake up. Oh. Goodness. Oh my god.
It's our...
Son! Our son! Oh, he's so cute.
Let's let them hope the baby.
Let's let them hold the baby.
Should we name him? Should we name him?
You're not going to hold it like a mommy?
Should should we name him?
Should we name him?
Yeah, we should name him.
We should let them name him. Them? Them? Them out there?
We should let them name him.
Them? Them? Them out there?
Yeah. They've been watching us this whole time, you know?
What? Do you guys have an idea? They have what? To name our baby? They've been watching?
What? Do you guys have an idea?
To name our baby?
They've been watching?
Give birth?
They're They're giving name suggestions. Then what?
Yeah.
Those are some great suggestions. What do you think?
All terrible.
I'm going to name him Neriji.
Neriji.
Yeah. Cuz it's like your name and then my name and together. And now...
It's perfect.
It's just a happy family. Just you, me, Neriji, and then now you're a beautiful mother, and now I'm also a beautiful father. What else can we do?
It's just a happy family.
Just you, me, Neriji,
and then now you're a beautiful mother,
and now you're a beautiful mother,
and then now I'm also a beautiful father. what else can we do?
and I'm a beautiful father. What else?
I don't know. Maybe you should go somewhere else while I take care of the baby.
Why are you still watching me? Go away!
Go away.
Better get the mail for my wife.
I think giving birth is really expensive.
What about to pay the bills?
I don't have any money though.
God, I hope these aren't bills.
Help!
Wait! Did you - did you leave your controller on?
Oh, maybe I like jogged on the floor and the controller like... Wait, you're not touching the controller!
Wait, she's going for the ladder! Well, take it out!
The liquid of water is filling your lungs and the air is slowly moving out of your body towards drowning...
Wait, she's kind of cute though.
Oh my god, what's happening? Oh my god, did you see that?
Uh, is the house on fire?
My house might be on fire.
Oh, fire!
Oh, whatever, it's fine.
Inhale, fill your lungs with water, you are slowly suffocating from the inside.
I hear the inner monologue.
Babe, who helped me?
I think there is a - a quiz function.
Oh, yeah. I think it's like if the character can answer the quiz correctly...
...the ladder will come back as a prize.
Wait, so much water!
Are you ready?
Wait, are you ready for the cleanse? Are you ready? What are you waiting for, the cleanse? Are you ready?
What is the name of the hypothetical particle that mediates the force of gravity in quantum field theory...
...and has not yet been observed experimentally?
A. Photon, B. Gluon, C. Graviton, or D. Neutrino.
Please answer correctly, or else you will die.
Wait, wait! Why are we going with D? It's D! I don't care, it's D!
I need a bigger water.
A! It's A!
The answer was C. Graviton! What do you mean?
Can I have a next chance? Well, I'm bored now. Oh well. Okay, boring.
Take my ladder away! Help me! Help me!
I don't know how to do that! Mori Calliope, give me a hand! Mori Calliope, I'm drowning!
Mori Calliope, help me!
She's flashing me while I'm dying? There's - there's a better time for that!
Stop! Stop! I can't look!
Mori Calliope, put that away!
Hey! Hey!
Listen to me, I'm drowning!
Listen to me. I'm okay.
You made me watch dancing fruits on TV.
You liked it.
You made me dance next to horses. I liked that.
Fuck you.
Wait, wait, we can talk about it! Mori Calliope, wait, what?
Die, idiot!
So - so help me, I'm drowning. Babe, babe, we're killing me. They're literally - they're already killing me.
Ah, boy Calliope, she's killing me.
I'm alive. I'm - I'm not drowning.
But my wife, my child, my beautiful wife and child, where are they? Why am I in the grim kingdom?
What about Nerissa? My beautiful wife! No!
Nerissa, where did you go? I love you!
Why is everything on fire?!
What?!
My friends are made out of cardboard!
They are not fire-resistant! Oh no.
Okay, I see that the Grimms are doing their best to save them.
Okay, Grimms, what - what's this one doing? What are you up to?
Oh, you are not helping at all. It's - it's okay, little Grimm. Your arms will reach one day.
These grems on the other hand,
you have magic!
Wow, where'd you learn this?
Gremurs are so talented.
Not you, though.
It's okay. One day...
Grems are working really hard, so
I, me, Gigi Murin, the hero, is here to save the day!
This must be my hero weapon, as all heroes have a hero weapon. Okay.
1 million dollars?
What? 1 million dollars?
Kingdom can save itself. I am not...
Oh wait, a catapult? Of course! Of course, obviously.
Okay, I'll help with this. Don't worry, Grems.
Let me...
What what ammo is here?
Okay, let's let's just pick this up.
Yay! Let's go, Grem! Let's save the kingdom!
Let's save the kingdom together!
We're barely scratching it.
I don't know what to do.
There's there's just no other choice.
I'm gonna have to pull out that move.
Yeah! Yeah, that move!
My ultimate move!
All right, everyone, are you ready to see my ultimate move? Okay.
Exult!
How did you scare me? Wait! No!
You took you took the fire from those Grem!
Stop it! Stop! You're gonna die!
No! No, you're getting hurt!
Please, I need you! If you're dead here, who's gonna tell me how to fight the dragon?
No! Don't! Please! Please!
You're getting hurt!
Don't! Don't!
Are you okay? Grem-chan? Are you okay?
You've saved me.
We must... this... Kingdom... How am I supposed to save it without you?
Grem-chan, no! I don't know how else to save the kingdom and destroy the dragon if it's not taking any damage.
Get up! Call the guard
wizard graveyard
Grems come and pray, Gremdal the Grey
Danger is here, a dragons appear
Come seize the day, fight and we slay
Gigi Murin, here at the scene
Look and behold, legends foretold
She is the brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
From near and far, hit by a car
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
gremurin, gremurin
Help! Call the guard
Grems come and pray
Danger is here, a dragons appear
Come seize the day, fight and we slay
Gigi Murin, here at the scene
Look and behold, legends foretold
She is the brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
From near and far, hit by a car
Joy she will bring, grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
gremurin, gremurin
Help! Call the guard
Grems come and pray
Danger is here, a dragons appear
She is the brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
I'm not an interpretive dancer!
From near and far, hit by a car
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gigi's here.
Don't worry.
Another cart wheel.
Another cartwheel.
A second one even!
Grems come and pray.
Danger is here, a dragons appear
Danger is here, a dragon appears
And then a worm.
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Is it working?
Is the dragon being cringed out by me?
Oh no, I cannot do this!
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Murin
Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi
It's a thing! It's a thing, my name!
Is it working?
Tell me, children!
Is the dragon be affected by me?
Help! Call the guard
They don't call me the fister for nothing!
Grems come and pray
gremurin, gremurin
Gigi Mu Rin
Gigi Murin
That's me, the fister
Here at the scene, Gigi Murin, holoLive English Justice
I've done it!
Gigi Murin have done it!
Gigi Murin has done it!
I defeated the dragon!
I did it!
Ojii-chan! It was all-thinks-to-you and the 15 children!
Ojii-chan! It was all thanks to you and the 15 children!
Yay!
Ojii-chan! Wait, you're still dead?
No. No, I thought I thought my power of dance could have saved you.
No, I thought my power of dance could have saved you.
Ojii-chan! No!
Ojii-chan! You're okay?
The power of dance does save everyone.
You're okay, right? You're not possessed, are you?
Oh, what is this?
Oh, what are you doing? Oh, what is happening?
Ojii-chan, what's what's happening? Oh god. What's what's happening?
Ojii-chan, what's happening? Oh god. What is happening?
What the... What the heck is happening?
Ojii-chan?
Ojii-chan! You're okay!
I've done it! Yay!
Behold, the darkness has lifted from the dragon's soul.
My final desperate strike has shattered its cruel memories.
No longer a beast of fury, it had been reborn as an innocent baby dragon!
No longer a beast of fury, it has been reborn as an innocent baby dragon!
おはこんばんちは (How are you?)
Ohakonbanchihwa (How are you?)
今日も今日とて最高です
Today is also the best day ever
おう~わんどほい!
Ooh~ Wonderhoy!
にっこり^^調査隊のテーマ
[Title: Nikkori^^ Survey Team Theme]
探索!コレクション!探索!
Exploration! Collection! Quest!
E・G・A・O
E-G-A-O
諸君(はい!)我々は世界の笑顔を調査する
We are here to survey the smiles of the world!
はい隊長 俺に名案が(却下)
Yes Captain, I have a great idea (Rejected!)
ってまだなにも言ってないんだが?
Wait, I haven't even said anything yet?
もー とーにーかく あれだほら
Geez, anyway, about that, you know
カバんは一見にしかず?
"A beetle in the hand is worth two in the bush"?
ああ 百聞は一見にしかずだね(それそれ!)
Ah, you mean "A picture is worth a thousand words" right? (Yes, that's it!)
つまり虫取り?(恐)(違うって)
So you mean catching bugs? (Fear) (No, that's not it!)
隊長!(なになに~/なんだ?)
Captain! (What is it? / What?)
提案があります
I have a proposal
是非聞かせてほしいものだな
I'd love to hear it
とりあえず(とりあえず?)
For now (For now?)
とりあえず出発しよう
For now, let's set off
ノープランで(うん!)
With no plan (Yeah!)
(ちょっと待って)(え?) 出発進行! ちょっと待ってって旅支度くらいさせろ~!
(Wait a second) (Eh?) Departure! Wait, at least let me pack!
数日後 持ち物チェックを始めまーす
A few days later... Let's start the item check
まずは基本のパパパ パスポーと もったい!
First, the basics! Passport check!
チッチッがえ忘れた でもスマホ バッテリーもった!
Gigi forgot it? But she has her smartphone and battery!
心ざしは持った!
Determination is set!
一番のガイデ 私がいる!
The best guide is right here!
しかも普通じゃない 誰のことかな?
And not just ordinary... Whose is it?
僕らには不可能を可能に変える力創るさ
We have the power to turn the impossible into possible
にっこりこりこりこりこりあんだ あっちもこっちもせんがくばんらい
Nikkori smiles everywhere!
君の笑顔も コレクションさせて!
Let me collect your smile too!
おとなもことも関係ねぇぜ これぞイチリューのエンターテイメント
Adults and kids alike, this is top-notch entertainment!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって
I'll make my dreams come true someday too!
このにっこりに触れて もっと胸膨らみそうさ
Touching these smiles will make our hearts swell even more!
にっこり^^調査隊
Niccori^^ Survey Team
おはこんばちは how are you?
Good morning, good evening, hello, how are you?
今日も今日とて最高です おう〜わんどほい！
Today is also the absolute best, ooh, wonderhoy!
探索! コレクション! 求索!
Exploration! Collection! Quest!
E・G・A・O
E-G-A-O
諸君 (はい!) 我々は世界の笑顔を調査する
Gentlemen, (Yes!) we are investigating smiles worldwide
はい隊長 俺に名案が... (却下!)ってまだなにも言ってないんだが？
Yes, Captain! I have a brilliant idea...
もー とーにーかーくー あれだほら カナブンは一見にしかず？
(Rejected!) Wait, I haven't even said anything yet!
あぁ 百聞は一見にしかずだね (それそれ!)
Ah, you mean seeing is believing, right?
つまり虫取り? (恐) (違うって)
So, bug catching? (Scared) (No, that's not it!)
隊長! (なになに~/なんだ?) 提案があります
Captain! (What is it?) I have a proposal.
ぜひ聞かせてほしいものだな
I'd love to hear it.
とりあえず (とりあえず?)
For now... (For now?)
とりあえず出発しよう ノープランで (うん!)
For now, let's depart with no plan! (Yeah!)
(ちょっと待って) (え?) 出発進行!
(Wait a second!) (Eh?) Departure!
ちょっと待ってって! 旅支度くらいさせろ~!
Wait a second! Let me at least pack my bags!
おはこんばちは how are you?
Good morning, good evening, hello, how are you?
パスポート? (もった!) チケット? (忘れちゃった!)
Passport? (Got it!) Ticket? (Forgot it!)
まーいっか! 行こっか!
That's fine! Let's go!
モバイルバッテリー? (持った!)
Mobile battery? (Got it!)
決意は? (持った!)
Determination? (Got it!)
モチベーション奥底からとか?
Motivation from the bottom of my heart? (Got it!)
悩みや悩みは あんましカンケーない
Troubles and worries? (Not really!)
ワールドワイドだぜ
The world is still wide open, right?
どっちも世界もまだまだ吸ってたもんじゃないだってね
Even if we're still just sipping juice...
りかりかりかりかり お里こさん
Sparkling, glittering, shining, we're the oricosan!
いらっしゃいょういらっしゃいようこそウェルカムウェルカム
Hey! Welcome, welcome, welcome, welcome!
きみの笑顔が調査隊仕様さ
Your smile is the survey destination!
イェイイェイイェイイェイイェイ!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
メンタルとカルチャおっけー?
Mental and physical condition OK?
キミパスポート持ってきて!
Keep your passport ready!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって
I'll make my dreams come true someday!
we can do it! さらに身近に触れて
We can do it! Let's get even closer!
もっと胸の奥から見知ったとさ
More bone-deep discoveries, got it?
そのしょんぼりをにっこりに変換
Turn that gloominess into sparkles!
うちらのハピネスメッキューはマキシマムあげのときだって下げのときだってかき混ぜちゃってスパイスだって!
Spreading our wings, our tension is maxed out!
りかりかりかりかり お里こじゃん
Sparkling, glittering, shining, we're the oricosan!
大人も子供もねぇぜ どっちも我>もう調査対象だ!
Adults and children are all our survey targets!
うぇるかむうぇるかむうぇるかむうぇるかむ
Hey! Welcome, welcome, welcome, welcome!
きみの笑顔が調査隊仕様さ
Your smile is the survey destination!
イェイイェイイェイイェイイェイ!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
メンタルとカルチャおっけー?
Mental and physical condition OK?
キミパスポート持ってきて!
Keep your passport ready!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって
I'll make my dreams come true someday!
we can do it! さらに身近に触れて
We can do it! Let's get even closer!
もっと骨の奥から見知ったとさ
More bone-deep discoveries, got it?
That's not all! That's right!
You didn't expect this? Oh, you didn't expect this!
There's 3D merch! Yay!
You too, you watching at home,
can own your very own...
Grem's Hand In Cushion!
What does that mean? You can put your hands in the Grem!
You can remember all the good times we had in the Grem Kingdom!
With Oto-chan! Yay! Yay!
And you can do so many things with this Grem,
like... stick your hands in it, which I said.
You can take your hands in the Grem,
and you can sleep on it, and you can squish it,
and you can cherish it, and you can love it!
And it's very soft and very squishy.
Just watch Oto-chan play with it, doesn't it look so cool?
3Dおひろめグッズの登場だ!
3D goods release!
やっほー! 見よ、このグレムのもちもちのハンドインクッションじゃよ!
Yay! Look, this Grem's squishy-squishy Hand In Cushion, yo!
いっぱい可愛がってあげよ~
Hehe, he'll be so happy if you spoil him!
頼んだぞ! やー!
I ordered it, too! Yay!
Thank you everyone for coming to my 3D live today!
I worked really, really hard on it!
And thank you to the staff who has been overseeing me!
And thank you for Gigi-chaf for being here!
And thank you for the Grems, and thank you for Mori Calliope, and Erissa, and Bae, Biboo, and Justice for being here a part of my 3D live!
It is so much fun.
Oh, it was so awesome!
Thank you, and I'm looking forward to doing more 3D things for you guys!
Yay! Yippee!
And don't, don't forget...
there is more 3D debuts next week!
So make sure you tune in because all of Justice has been working so hard, okay? Okay?
Bye everyone!
I'll see you later! Bye-bye!